Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Let's split up and replenish
our traveling supplies.
"Split up"? You've assigned me
most of the necessities.
Food, water, daily essentials.
What are you going to buy?
Herbs and stuff.
That's the face she makes when
she's hiding something from me.
I've known Ms. Frieren for a long time.
Nothing good ever happens
when she makes that face.
She's definitely going to buy
something we don't need.
I bought this.
What are you going to use that for?
This potion only dissolves clothing.
Go return it.
It's a book on magical history.
Classroom study is important, too.
Well, I wouldn't call that one unnecessary.
I'll meet you at the inn later.
We can't afford to waste
our traveling funds.
I'd better keep a close eye on her.
An accessory shop?
You went to sleep without
drying your hair again.
So she's interested in fashion after all.
She seems really conflicted.
What's with that face?
I've never seen Ms. Frieren
look so troubled before.
She spent a lot of time on that.
I suppose an accessory wouldn't hurt.
It's better than weird bones or medicines.
Maybe I'll resume my shopping soon.
Is there a shop around here
that sells good desserts?
Now that's not fair.
There's a tavern in the basement
of that building. Try asking there.
Thank you.
I haven't eaten anything sweet in months!
This must be it.
Is there a shop around here
that sells good desserts?
This clearly isn't the right
place to ask about desserts.
A dessert joint? Who do you
think you're talking to?
Gulp.
You better believe this city's got
mountains of delicious desserts.
We can recommend you places all over.
So they do know about desserts here.
For such rough-looking guys,
you know a lot about desserts.
A bit of sugar gives us the energy
we need to adventure.
Nothing beats rewarding yourself with
something sweet after a hard day's work.
So they're adventurers. Though I'd say
even "rough" is an understatement.
They're terrifying.
See ya.
Is she going to a dessert shop?
Huh? She's heading in
the direction of our inn.
Is she going back?
I'm not even close to finishing my shopping.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Well, no matter. Put your things down.
Shall we go get something sweet to eat?
What a nice view. No wonder
they recommended this place.
Ms. Frieren, I'm sorry for doubting you.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Choose whatever you'd like.
Can we afford it?
I've been saving up secretly.
She's been keeping secret savings?
Ms. Frieren, what will you have?
Well, today I feel like...
Merkur pudding, right?
You feel like eating Merkur
pudding today, don't you?
How did you know?
How many years do you think
we've traveled together?
I can just tell.
I don't know anything about the rest of you.
Then maybe I'll try harder
to teach you about myself.
Incidentally, my favorite
food is Ruf-omelette.
Mine's grapes. The sourer, the better.
Mine is—
Alcohol, right?
I knew that already, you corrupt priest.
That's nothing to blush about.
It's not a good sign that the one thing
she remembers is your drinking.
Fern, I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I don't know anything about you,
so I don't know what you like.
Come to think of it, it's my birthday today.
What a beautiful hair ornament.
Thank you. I'm delighted.
Really?
You seem to be hopelessly dense,
so let me be clear.
I'm overjoyed that you
tried to get to know me.
Only because I tried?
You really don't understand
people's feelings, do you?
Shall we get going?
Sure.
By the way, Ms. Frieren,
does this journey have a purpose?
Not particularly. I'm satisfying
my desire to collect spells.
But whenever possible,
I'd like to retrace the adventures
I had with Himmel and the others
before all sign of them fades away.
That's something important to you, right?
I don't know, so I'm trying
to figure that out.
You've finally grown taller than me.
I'm sixteen now. I could be your older sister.
My older sister?
Our diets are mostly the same,
so it can't be that.
How strange.
You've grown quite accustomed
to casting defensive spells.
Let's put that into practice.
What?
I aimed for the gaps in your defenses.
If this had been a real battle, you'd be dead.
Now, then...
How will you handle this?
Like this.
I see.
Can you withstand this?
That's enough for today.
Defensive magic is powerful,
but it rapidly depletes your mana.
You'll exhaust your mana supply in seconds
if you try to maintain it over a large area.
So the best option is to cast it in select
locations at the moment of impact.
Exactly.
Hup.
We've been practicing nothing
but defensive magic.
It directly improves your chances of survival.
You're right.
A single defensive spell can defend
against most offensive spells.
It's strange how powerful they are.
Fern, you haven't read the book on
magical history I gave you, have you?
Magic is about theory as much as practice.
I suppose I'll have to read
it to you at bedtime.
I'll read it myself.
I'm not a child, after all.
This village is where you wanted to go, right?
Are you here to collect odd spells again?
No, not this time.
Now it's up to the weather.
Yeah.
I have a question.
It's an elf.
White hair...
Are you Ms. Frieren?
How did you know?
You're here to see the place where
Qual was sealed, aren't you?
I'll show you the way.
Qual?
The Elder Sage of Corruption, Qual.
He's a demon who committed terrible
atrocities in this region eighty years ago,
before being sealed away
by Himmel the Hero and his party.
That seal will break soon,
so I'm here to defeat him,
but how did you know?
I haven't told anyone about this.
Mr. Himmel visited this town every year
until about thirty years ago.
He was apparently checking
on the condition of the seal.
He always was a softie.
He used to talk about you.
He called you heartless
for not checking on him.
She's cold, isn't she?
Quite cold.
Sorry about that.
But she's not so heartless that
she'd leave the village to its fate.
She'll come when the seal is about to break.
That's what he said.
I see.
This is it?
It's become rather unstable.
I'll dispel the seal tomorrow
and take care of Qual.
You're the one who sealed Qual, aren't you?
Is there a reason you did that?
He was simply too strong.
I couldn't beat him.
Even among the Demon King's forces,
Qual was an exceptional mage.
He developed the first piercing spell
in history, which he called Zoltraak.
It pierced not only defensive spells but
the magic resistance of armor as well.
It directly targeted and destroyed the body.
It's said that in this region,
40% of adventurers and 70% of mages
were killed by Zoltraak.
That's too powerful.
Yes, it was. Much too powerful.
And that's why it backfired on him.
What do you mean?
You really haven't read that
history tome, have you?
Are you sure I shouldn't read it to you?
I'll start reading it right now.
No, it's fine.
It's more important that
you get a good night's sleep.
You'll see tomorrow, anyway.
I'm dispelling the seal.
Don't let your guard down.
It's been a while, Frieren.
How many years has it been?
Eighty.
A mere eighty years, huh?
For us, anyway.
And the Demon King?
We killed him.
I see.
Then I shall avenge him.
Fern, cast a defensive spell in front of us.
Zoltraak!
I'm surprised.
You blocked Zoltraak.
That defensive spell of yours
must be powerful indeed.
Ms. Frieren, what's going on?
That was ordinary offensive magic.
That's Zoltraak.
The killing magic he developed.
Qual, your magic was simply too powerful.
After you were sealed away, mages across
the land studied and analyzed Zoltraak.
In just a few years, Zoltraak was
incorporated into humankind's magic system,
and powerful new defensive spells
were developed.
The magic resistance offered by equipment
has improved significantly as well,
making Zoltraak no longer killing magic.
Now it's just "ordinary offensive magic."
Eighty years is quite a long time for humans.
Qual, if you don't resist,
I'll make your death painless.
I see.
I see, I see.
It attunes itself to the offensive
magic and disperses its power.
A complex spell indeed.
It must consume a great deal of mana.
He figured out the weakness
of defensive magic.
Fern, you know what to do, right?
Yes. I saw it in our practices.
Then protect me as well.
So you can fly? Interesting.
Zoltraak.
Frieren... My spell...
Now we can live in peace.
That hat...
This thing?
Around here, the sun's rays are strong
even at this time of year,
so all farmers wear them.
I've seen this hat before.
You're the brat who flipped my skirt up.
Take that!
What do you think you're doing, brat?
I'll kill you! You saw what I've
been wanting to see all this time!
You'd better not kill him.
I'll show you mine.
Yikes.
You're still alive.
Thanks to you,
I'll be able to live even longer.
I'm glad I trusted Himmel's words and waited.
Ms. Frieren, they thanked you.
They didn't thank me.
The people of this village
believed in Himmel.
I don't understand, exactly,
but I think Mr. Himmel believed in you.
What is it?
Nothing.
Because I felt sorry for you.
Because it's more convenient that way.
She was an irresponsible person.
That's enough depressing talk.
Are you sure you haven't been
around since prehistoric times?
You're more conscientious than you look.
It was a long time ago.
Aureole, the land where souls rest.